Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Correspondence.
  - Attorneys. Miscellaneous., 1976-1985; 1 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 21.
  - Attorney Fees. Monthly Breakdown., 2 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00220 on Files reel 21.
  - Alper, Schoene, Horkan & Mann., 3 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00242 on Files reel 21.
  - Brundage, Davis, Frommer & Jesinger., 4 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00270 on Files reel 21.
  - Calihan, Edward J., Jr. Chicago, IL., 5 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00305 on Files reel 21.
  - Davis, Cowell & Bowe., 6 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00362 on Files reel 21.
  - Davis, Frommer., 7 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00382 on Files reel 21.
  - Feder, Gerald M., Washington, DC., 1976-1980; 8 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00427 on Files reel 21.
  - Feder, Gerald M., Washington, DC., 1981; 9 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00620 on Files reel 21.
  - Horkan & Berry., 10 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00747 on Files reel 21.
  - Iverson, Yoakum, Papiano & Hatch., 11 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00775 on Files reel 21.
  - Katz, Charles. Attorney., 12 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00852 on Files reel 21.
  - Katz, Jonas B. Cincinnati, OH., 1979-1980; 13 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 00868 on Files reel 21.
  - Katz, Jonas B., 1981-1985; 14 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01007 on Files reel 21.
  - Kircher & Phalen, Cincinnati, OH., 15 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01224 on Files reel 21.
  - Levy & Goldman. Attorneys, 16 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01369 on Files reel 21.
  - Linehan, Edward T. St. Louis, MO., 1978-1980; 17 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01427 on Files reel 21.
  - Linehan, Edward T., 1981-1982; 18 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01638 on Files reel 21.
  - Mozer, Robert J. New York, NY., 19 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01748 on Files reel 21.
  - Pinales, Martin S. Attorney. Cincinnati, OH., 20 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01827 on Files reel 21.
  - Reynolds, John J. Chicago, IL., 1979-1980; 21 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 01910 on Files reel 21.
  - Reynolds, John J. Chicago, IL., 1981; 22 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 02136 on Files reel 21.
  - Reynolds, John J. Chicago, IL., 1982; 23 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 02217 on Files reel 21.
  - Reynolds, John J. Chicago, IL., 1985; 24 (Reel 21)
    Beginning at frame 02607 on Files reel 21.
  - Sabbeth, Dennis. Attorney., 1 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 22.
  - Johnson, Morsinger, Trismen & Sharp. Winter Park, FL., 2 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00048 on Files reel 22.
  - Rotatori, Robert J. Cleveland, OH., 3 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00193 on Files reel 22.
  - Walsh, Carl M., Chicago, IL, 4 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00241 on Files reel 22.
  - Amalgamated Bank. Chicago, IL., 1987-1990; 5 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00255 on Files reel 22.
  - Amalgamated Bank. New York, NY., 1984-1990; 6 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00359 on Files reel 22.
  - Aetna Life Insurance. Enrollment Forms., 1979; 7 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00363 on Files reel 22.
  - Aetna Life Insurance., 1979-1982; 8 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00460 on Files reel 22.
  - Aetna Life Insurance. Closed., 1983-1989; 9 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00697 on Files reel 22.
  - Aetna Life Insurance. Form Letters., 1979-1988; 10 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 00936 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO., 1977; 11 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01216 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO., 1979; 12 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01323 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Affiliated Unions., 1972-1982; 13 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01391 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades., 1962-1981; 14 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01460 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. C.O.P.E., 1971-1982; 15 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01532 on Files reel 22.
  - Contributions from C.O.P.E. Account., 1972-1973; 16 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 01676 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Food and Beverage Trades Department., 1977; 17 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02019 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Food and Beverage Trades Department., 1979; 18 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02048 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Maritime Trades Department., 1977; 19 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02086 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Maritime Trades Department., 1979; 20 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02131 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. U.L. & S.T. Department., 1977; 21 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02161 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. U.L. & S.T. Department., 1979; 22 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02214 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. George Meaney, President., 1975-1980; 23 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02264 on Files reel 22.
  - AFL-CIO. Credit Union., 1985-1990; 24 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02320 on Files reel 22.
  - Allgeier Associates., 1983-1985; 25 (Reel 22)
    Beginning at frame 02501 on Files reel 22.
  - American Airlines., 1975-1984; 1 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 23.
  - American Airlines. Travel Cards. Correspondence., 1983-1984; 2 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00151 on Files reel 23.
  - American Airlines. Air Travel., 1985-1990; 3 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00253 on Files reel 23.
  - American Airlines., 1985-1990; 4 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00516 on Files reel 23.
  - American Express Co., 1980-1990; 5 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00817 on Files reel 23.
  - American Express Co. Management Reports., 1985-1990; 6 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 00967 on Files reel 23.
  - Amerianc Pest Management., 1985; 7 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01301 on Files reel 23.
  - American Savings., 1986-1988; 8 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01306 on Files reel 23.
  - American Security Bank. Closed., 1984; 9 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01349 on Files reel 23.
  - AMIVEST. General Correspondence., 1983-1989; 10 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01557 on Files reel 23.
  - AMIVEST. Portfolio Valuations. Closed., 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01655 on Files reel 23.
  - ASPNOVA, 1989; 12 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01811 on Files reel 23.
  - Associated Membership. Closed., 1986-1988; 13 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01847 on Files reel 23.
  - AT&T., 1985-1990; 14 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 01995 on Files reel 23.
  - Attronica Computers, Inc., 15 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 02042 on Files reel 23.
  - Auditel., 1985-1990; 16 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 02106 on Files reel 23.
  - Automobile. Correspondence., 1986-1989; 17 (Reel 23)
    Beginning at frame 02381 on Files reel 23.
  - Automobile. Correspondence., 1990; 1 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 24.
  - Automobiles. IRS., 1985-1990; 2 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 00280 on Files reel 24.
  - Auto Leases., 1985-1987; 3 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 00646 on Files reel 24.
  - Auto Leases., 1988; 4 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 00958 on Files reel 24.
  - Auto Leases., 1989-1990; 5 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01105 on Files reel 24.
  - Bell Atlantic., 6 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01306 on Files reel 24.
  - "B" Miscellaneous., 1989; 7 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01323 on Files reel 24.
  - Bonds (Blanket Master). U.S.F.&G., 1961-1977; 8 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01337 on Files reel 24.
  - Bookkeeping., 1984-1990; 9 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01684 on Files reel 24.
  - Burroughs Corp., 1983-1988; 10 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01862 on Files reel 24.
  - "C" Miscellaneous., 1987-1990; 11 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01897 on Files reel 24.
  - Canadian Labour Congress. Correspondence., 1968-1975; 12 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 01922 on Files reel 24.
  - Canadian Regional Office., 1989-1990; 13 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 02082 on Files reel 24.
  - Catering Industry Employee., 1984-1990; 14 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 02107 on Files reel 24.
  - Cheek, Marsha., 1976-1983; 15 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 02468 on Files reel 24.
  - Communications., 1988-1990; 16 (Reel 24)
    Beginning at frame 02595 on Files reel 24.
  - Computerization., 1983-1990; 1 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 25.
  - Condo-Plaza., 1984-1989; 2 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00178 on Files reel 25.
  - Condo-Plaza., 1990; 3 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00396 on Files reel 25.
  - Condo-New York, NY., 1990; 4 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00550 on Files reel 25.
  - Continental Bank Illinois. Closed., 1982-1986; 5 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00577 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School., 1985-1988; 6 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00646 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School., 1989-1990; 7 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 00877 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School. Interior., 1985-1988; 8 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01117 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School. Construction., 1983-1988; 9 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01246 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School. Occupancy., 1985-1986; 10 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01506 on Files reel 25.
  - Corcoran School. Relocation., 1982-1984; 11 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01673 on Files reel 25.
  - Courier/Express System., 1986-1990; 12 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01850 on Files reel 25.
  - "D" Miscellaneous., 13 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01946 on Files reel 25.
  - Datacomp Leasing. Closed., 1983-1984; 14 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 01977 on Files reel 25.
  - DC Department of Finance and Revenue., 1975-1990; 15 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02007 on Files reel 25.
  - Dexel Software., 16 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02184 on Files reel 25.
  - Dictaphone. Closed., 1985-1992; 17 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02237 on Files reel 25.
  - Direct Billing Applications., 1985-1989; 18 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02263 on Files reel 25.
  - Direct Deposit Program., 1986-1990; 19 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02288 on Files reel 25.
  - District of Columbia. Miscellaneous., 1989-1990; 20 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02496 on Files reel 25.
  - Dupont Building., 1985-1990; 21 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02516 on Files reel 25.
  - Eastern Airlines., 1989; 22 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02753 on Files reel 25.
  - Eastern Business Machines (EBM). Maint. And Service Agreements., 1988-1989; 23 (Reel 25)
    Beginning at frame 02784 on Files reel 25.
  - Employers Identification Numbers. IRS., 1982-1990; 1 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 26.
  - Employer Lunch Program., 1988-1989; 2 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00254 on Files reel 26.
  - Dupont Building. Rentals., 1986-1990; 3 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00269 on Files reel 26.
  - Entre Computer Center., 1988-1990; 4 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00488 on Files reel 26.
  - Expense Reimbursement Policy., 1990; 5 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00578 on Files reel 26.
  - "F" Miscellaneous., 1987-1989; 6 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00594 on Files reel 26.
  - Fifty-Year Pins., 1983-1988; 7 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00613 on Files reel 26.
  - Fifty-Year Pins., 1989-1990; 8 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00828 on Files reel 26.
  - Filings. State/Local., 1985-1989; 9 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 00980 on Files reel 26.
  - First Commercial Bank. Chicago, IL. Closed., 1991; 10 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01006 on Files reel 26.
  - First National. Cincinnati, OH. Closed., 1981-1991; 11 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01085 on Files reel 26.
  - First National. Strike File., 12 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01164 on Files reel 26.
  - First National. Cincinnati, OH., 1984-1989; 13 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01257 on Files reel 26.
  - Fisher, Marilee., 1981-1983; 14 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01586 on Files reel 26.
  - Form Letters., 1980-1990; 15 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 01697 on Files reel 26.
  - Fund Trust. Closed., 1986; 16 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 02052 on Files reel 26.
  - Gilburn, Hugh., 1985-1988; 17 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 02068 on Files reel 26.
  - Ginns., 1984-1990; 18 (Reel 26)
    Beginning at frame 02346 on Files reel 26.
  - Give Aways., 1987-1990; 1 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 27.
  - Glass & Glass, CPA., 1984-1987; 2 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00255 on Files reel 27.
  - Goldberg, David, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 3 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00289 on Files reel 27.
  - Government Investors, DC. Closed., 1982-1984; 4 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00418 on Files reel 27.
  - Guernsey Office Products., 1985-1990; 5 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00462 on Files reel 27.
  - "H" Miscellaneous., 1990; 6 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00558 on Files reel 27.
  - HERE Assets, Liabilities & Fund Balances., 1987-1990; 7 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 00571 on Files reel 27.
  - HERE Computer Program., 1988-1990; 8 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01000 on Files reel 27.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Credit Cards., 9 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01297 on Files reel 27.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Receipts and Disbursements., 1989-1990; 10 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01329 on Files reel 27.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Welfare/Pension Funds., 1987-1990; 11 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01579 on Files reel 27.
  - Hormel Strike., 12 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01819 on Files reel 27.
  - "I" Miscellaneous., 1988-1990; 13 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 01988 on Files reel 27.
  - IBM Corporation., 1984-1990; 14 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 02003 on Files reel 27.
  - Imigration Act., 1987-1990; 15 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 02272 on Files reel 27.
  - INFOTXT., 1983-1989; 16 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 02338 on Files reel 27.
  - Insurance International Union., 1988-1989; 17 (Reel 27)
    Beginning at frame 02452 on Files reel 27.
  - Insurance. International., 1990; 1 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 28.
  - International Insurance Consultants., 1980-1981; 2 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00188 on Files reel 28.
  - International Insurance Consultants., 1982; 3 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00461 on Files reel 28.
  - "J" Miscellaneous., 1988-1990; 4 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00686 on Files reel 28.
  - JAL/NIKKO, 1988-1990; 5 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00753 on Files reel 28.
  - J. D. Edwards Co., 1985-1987; 6 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 00928 on Files reel 28.
  - JMB Insurance., 1983-1986; 7 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01017 on Files reel 28.
  - Juliano, Robert., 1983-1990; 8 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01273 on Files reel 28.
  - Kamber Group., 1989-1990; 9 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01508 on Files reel 28.
  - Kelly Press., 1985-1990; 10 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01513 on Files reel 28.
  - Kenwood Associates. Closed., 1987; 11 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01710 on Files reel 28.
  - "L" Miscellaneous., 1989-1990; 12 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01724 on Files reel 28.
  - LA Health/Welfare., 1988-1990; 13 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01763 on Files reel 28.
  - Lee, Raymond., 1976-1984; 14 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 01854 on Files reel 28.
  - Lee, Raymond, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 15 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02040 on Files reel 28.
  - "M" Miscellaneous., 1989-1990; 16 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02141 on Files reel 28.
  - MBI. Closed., 1986-1987; 17 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02205 on Files reel 28.
  - Marquardt Printing. Local Usage Supplements., 1988-1990; 18 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02241 on Files reel 28.
  - Marquardt Printing. Miscellaneous Orders., 1987-1988; 19 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02400 on Files reel 28.
  - Marquardt Printing. Miscellaneous Orders., 1989-1990; 20 (Reel 28)
    Beginning at frame 02651 on Files reel 28.
  - Marquardt Printing. Receipt Book Orders., 1988-1990; 1 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 29.
  - MD SASS. General. Closed., 1986-1990; 2 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00183 on Files reel 29.
  - MD SASS. Memorandums (Investment), 1987-1989; 3 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00416 on Files reel 29.
  - Members-At-Large Dues. Payments., 1983-1990; 4 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00671 on Files reel 29.
  - Memoes., 1985-1990; 5 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00836 on Files reel 29.
  - Merlin Aircraft. Closed., 1982-1989; 6 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 00974 on Files reel 29.
  - Micro Mart., 7 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01240 on Files reel 29.
  - Mid-Western Regional Office., 1985-1990; 8 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01269 on Files reel 29.
  - Monroe Systems., 1985-1990; 9 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01513 on Files reel 29.
  - N.S.&T. Bank. Washington, DC. Closed., 1983-1985; 10 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01615 on Files reel 29.
  - National Co-Ordinating Committee for Multi-Employer Plans., 1988-1990; 11 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01715 on Files reel 29.
  - National Rainbow Coalition., 1990; 12 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01802 on Files reel 29.
  - National Westminster Bank. Closed., 1983-1984; 13 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01836 on Files reel 29.
  - New York Hotel Trades Council., 1985-1990; 14 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01855 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department., 1981; 15 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 01882 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department., 1982; 16 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 02065 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department., 1983; 17 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 02159 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department., 1984; 18 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 02430 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department., 1985; 19 (Reel 29)
    Beginning at frame 02479 on Files reel 29.
  - Organizing Department. (continued)., 1985; 1 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing Department., 1987; 2 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00212 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing. Correspondence., 1985-1990; 3 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00232 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing Projects. H.E.R.E. Boston, 1985-1987; 4 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00401 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing. Chicago., 1985-1990; 5 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00479 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing Projects. H.E.R.E. D.C., 6 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00629 on Files reel 30.
  - Organizing Projects. H.E.R.E. Orange County., 7 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00704 on Files reel 30.
  - Office Expenses. Miscellaneous., 1986-1990; 8 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00785 on Files reel 30.
  - OPEIU. Local 98., 1983-1990; 9 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 00942 on Files reel 30.
  - Optical Plan. Closed., 1985-1990; 10 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01058 on Files reel 30.
  - Orton, Robert, Auditor., 1981-1983; 11 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01294 on Files reel 30.
  - Orton, Robert, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 12 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01432 on Files reel 30.
  - Palm Springs Regional., 1989-1990; 13 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01463 on Files reel 30.
  - Perry, David., 1977-1983; 14 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01491 on Files reel 30.
  - Perry, David Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 15 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01651 on Files reel 30.
  - Pershing Account., 1989-1990; 16 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01707 on Files reel 30.
  - Phoenix Systems., 1985-1990; 17 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01763 on Files reel 30.
  - Pitney Bowes., 1981-1986; 18 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01825 on Files reel 30.
  - Research Department. Los Angeles., 1990; 19 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01852 on Files reel 30.
  - Reynolds, John J., 1989-1990; 20 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 01949 on Files reel 30.
  - Rhinelander Regional Office., 1989-1990; 21 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 02028 on Files reel 30.
  - Riggs National Bank., 1984-1989; 22 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 02043 on Files reel 30.
  - Riggs National Bank., 1990; 23 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 02352 on Files reel 30.
  - Riggs Treasury Notes., 1985-1990; 24 (Reel 30)
    Beginning at frame 02421 on Files reel 30.
  - ROLM, 1984-1990; 1 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 31.
  - Ruiz, Daniel, Administrative Aide. Correspondence., 1990; 2 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00363 on Files reel 31.
  - "S" Miscellaneous., 1986-1990; 3 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00417 on Files reel 31.
  - SBS Skyline. Closed., 1985-1986; 4 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00449 on Files reel 31.
  - Scimeca, Anthony, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 5 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00558 on Files reel 31.
  - State Labor Councils Listings., 1987-1989; 6 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00613 on Files reel 31.
  - Stephenson, Arlene., 1982-1983; 7 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00767 on Files reel 31.
  - stephenson, Arlene, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 8 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00870 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. Las Vegas., 1984; 9 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 00871 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. April., 1984; 10 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01038 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. May 1-15., 1984; 11 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01215 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. May 16-31., 1984; 12 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01384 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. June 1-15., 1984; 13 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01489 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. June 16-30., 1984; 14 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01676 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. July 1-31., 1984; 15 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 01878 on Files reel 31.
  - Strike Fund. August 1-15., 1984; 16 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02072 on Files reel 31.
  - Sullivan & Almy. Closed., 1983-1984; 17 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02186 on Files reel 31.
  - TIP Education Fund., 1986-1990; 18 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02227 on Files reel 31.
  - Three M., 1986-1987; 19 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02257 on Files reel 31.
  - Unified Services., 1985-1988; 20 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02287 on Files reel 31.
  - Union Friendly., 1990; 21 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02311 on Files reel 31.
  - Union Labor Life Insurance., 1985-1990; 22 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02444 on Files reel 31.
  - Valverde, Lydia, Auditor. Correspondence., 1990; 23 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02511 on Files reel 31.
  - Vending Machines., 1987-1990; 24 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02526 on Files reel 31.
  - Vendors. Miscellaneous. Closed, 1986-1989; 25 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02562 on Files reel 31.
  - Vision Service Plan., 1990; 26 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02641 on Files reel 31.
  - "W" Miscellaneous., 1988-1990; 27 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02677 on Files reel 31.
  - Washington Update., 1983; 28 (Reel 31)
    Beginning at frame 02694 on Files reel 31.
  - Western Regional., 1985-1990; 1 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 32.
  - Wilhelm. CA & NV Locals., 1990; 2 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 00380 on Files reel 32.
  - Winner, Wagner & Associates., 1990; 3 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 00585 on Files reel 32.
  - Wood, Thomas E. Insurance., 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 00677 on Files reel 32.
  - Wood, Thomas E. Insurance., 1988-1990; 5 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 00989 on Files reel 32.
  - Workers Compensation., 1989-1990; 6 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01237 on Files reel 32.
  - Xerox., 1980-1990; 7 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01250 on Files reel 32.
  - AFL-CIO. Credit Union., 1991; 8 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01429 on Files reel 32.
  - Air Travel., 1991; 9 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01510 on Files reel 32.
  - American Express., 1991; 10 (Reel 32)